sup everyone it's for the kiss you're
not gonna believe what just happening I
just escaped being held captive from
Obama and George Bush for the pay I
don't know how long
how'd you guess it was like Apache or
some [ __ ] how'd you got dark take a
smelly ass dumped over in the bushes
I've been out in the wild for I think I
could week now I don't have any sports
candy with me no weapon no weapons and
[ __ ] although I'm gonna meet with a guy
I don't know who he is but he told me
he'd meet me here
he was good yummy weapon oh [ __ ] oh yeah
there it is [ __ ] pop tapping those
[ __ ] ass damn got take another
dumping [ __ ] I don't know why I'm going
they tried to make me they tried to make
me talk but I didn't say [ __ ] I did not
spill the beans tell him we were five I
do not spill the beans
I got away hello
where you at will ya [ __ ] the gospel to
me he's around here somewhere I don't
have it [ __ ] cool words that yo come out
[ __ ] hey you over there step back
listener I can't thank you enough over
what you will eat leave my smelly ass
back there
I've been in captivity for so long
nearly a year now so where we have now
no no idea no wha they did whatever they
could to get out of me to spank my ass
and call me daddy
damn boy now I'm doing good it sports
game there for you if you need
cool that without really revitalize my
strength but just in case
God does got this gun you gave me it'll
really come in handy boy what the [ __ ]
you talk about want you said the only
enemy was over with Obama I'm coming
[ __ ] what's going on doc Boyle what the
[ __ ] is that
well doc lawyer
what are they embody me for hatred of
Sonic and the game itself
hey yo open what that skin in your pants
or just put myself all we got to do that
first
who are you who are you Sportacus stay
back
it's the DAF warrior it's the army that
will send you take us down to stop the
prophecy
[Music]
dammit over one got away waiting for to
get away that's cool I gotta take a [ __ ]
I bet you do a war now that we see our
faces they're gonna be coming after both
of us damn what's gaff and we got there
would be there hopefully don't worry dr.
Walter yes you've been recording this
entire event haven't you
ha ha all happens you came through one
two three four five easy to page what
poses hopefully he sees this if he does
hopefully he'll come to help us
everybody comment down in the comments
below
tilting over five what is going on he is
the only one that can save save the wall
on the wall a war is coming
we need to rally an army it's the only
way we're going to dance we beat the
Warriors of that floor don't forget to
like this comment so so more people can
see it ain't 100 p45 no they're the love
for shotgun is still so powerful even to
this day look to the [ __ ] time that
is hope that we will win the war that
the prom piece speaks all come on slore
the kiss we need to go places be sir
you